buffalobills.com 2019-07-31

# Buffalo Bills Privacy Policy | Buffalo Bills - buffalobills.com

**Effective Date: December 15, 2013, revised November 5, 2015, August 31, 2016, November 16, 2016, January 17, 2017, January 30, 2018, July 24, 2019 ​**

This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") applies to the only official websites of the Buffalo Bills accessible at [www.buffalobills.com](http://www.buffalobills.com/) and m.buffalobills.com (collectively, the "Website"). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to disclose to you what information we may collect, how we may collect it, with whom we may share it, and certain other matters related to such information, including the choices you have regarding our collection of information and our use and disclosure to other parties of information we may have collected from you.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S. based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

The Website is operated by Buffalo Bills, LLC (“Buffalo Bills”, “we”, “our”, or “us”). We have contracted with third parties, including, without limitation, Delaware North Companies, to operate certain aspects of the Site on our behalf, including certain subscription products and services.

We own the information collected via the Website and we may use it for our own purposes, including marketing. Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected on the Website and through the Buffalo Bills mobile applications, which include the official Buffalo Bills team app (collectively referred to herein as the “Mobile App”).

When this Privacy Policy uses the term "personally identifiable information" or "personal information," we mean information that identifies a particular individual, such as your full name, street address or email address. When other information, such as a favorite team or player, is associated with personal information, it also becomes personally identifiable information for the purposes of this privacy policy.

Please read the information below to learn more about our data collection policies and practices.

1\. TYPES OF INFORMATION THAT MAY BE COLLECTED

The following are the types of information we may collect:

Information You Provide Us

In the course of using the Website, we may ask you to provide us with certain information, including contact information (such as your name, mailing address, email address, phone number, or fax number), unique identifiers (such as your user ID or user password), demographic information (such as your date of birth or age), access to your geo-location (location services using the Mobile App), and financial information (such as your credit card number) or similar information.

Website Usage Information

We may receive and store certain types of internet usage information whenever you visit the Website, such as your click-stream data and your IP address. See "IP Addresses and Click Stream Data" section below.

Email Communications

When you open emails from us, we may receive a confirmation notifying us that you opened the email, if your computer supports such capabilities. We also may keep track of what emails we send you and what emails you may be receiving from our subsidiaries and affiliates. Additionally, we keep a record of what communications you have selected to receive or not to receive. If you would like to opt-out of receiving such emails, please click on the "unsubscribe" link in the email and follow the instructions.

Information from Other Sources

We may receive information about you (e.g., missing street number) from other sources, such as the US Postal Service and add it to your personal information to verify your address so we can properly ship your order to you and prevent fraud.

2\. HOW INFORMATION MAY BE COLLECTED

We may collect information from you in several different areas on the Website, including but not limited to those described below:

Registration

You may be asked to complete a registration form and provide personally identifiable information; you may also be asked to choose a user ID and password in order to take advantage of certain features the Website may choose to offer, including but not limited to, Newsletters, Contests, Sweepstakes, Forums, Message Boards or other subscription-based products/services. Your decision to register is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to us and what communications you would like to receive; however, please be advised that many products and services available on the Website require registration and if you elect not to provide such information, you will not be able to take advantage of those products and services.

Contests or Sweepstakes

We periodically operate contests and sweepstakes through or promoted on the Website and/or Mobile App that will require registration or the submission of personal information. Your personally identifiable information may be used to contact you for winner notification, prize delivery confirmation or other related purposes (see the rules of each contest or sweepstakes for details about how your personal information will be used, including postings to the Website). In some instances, a third party advertiser or sponsor may operate or host a contest or sweepstakes on the Website, and collect your information. In those cases, where we are not the operator or host of the contest or sweepstakes, we have no control over the information collected and accordingly urge you to review the advertiser’s or sponsor’s privacy policy applicable to the contest or sweepstakes before participating.

Newsletters and Site Emails

We may offer newsletters to share information with you about the Website, about the Buffalo Bills, or about our affiliates, business partners, advertisers and sponsors. You may receive a newsletter either by registering for a particular newsletter or in conjunction with a special feature or membership for which you have registered on the Website. You may cancel your free email subscription by following the instructions provided on the Website or, in some instances, in the designated area of certain newsletters or emails.

Surveys or Voting

From time-to-time we may request personally identifiable information from you in conjunction with a survey or voting poll. Participation is voluntary, and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website. At times, you may have to register to vote or to take part in a survey.

Games

When you register to play games promoted on our Website, you may be asked to provide personally identifiable information.

Cookies

As with many websites, the Website uses a technology called "cookies." A cookie is a collection of information that gets stored on the hard drive of your computer when browsing the Internet. These small bits of code automatically identify your browser to the Website whenever your computer is used to visit the Website. Cookies also let us know how many people visit the Website and where visitors go on the Website. In addition, cookies can let us know non-personally identifiable information, like how many times a user has been on certain pages. For registered users, cookies can make using the Website easier for you by saving information such as your passwords or preferences. By tracking how and when you use the Website, cookies help us determine which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the Website are based on data obtained from cookies. Accepting cookies allows you, among other things, to personalize your experience on the Website. Cookies may also allow the Website to present to you advertising which may be of interest to you. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, your browser should contain an option that allows you to disable or delete cookie data at any time. Some areas of the Website, however, may not provide you with a personalized experience if you have disabled the use of cookies. Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our Website. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by this Website only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Flash LSOs

We use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences such as volume control or display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit. Third Parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, use Flash cookies to collect and store information.

Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies please visit:

Web Beacons and Other Tracking Technology

The Website and Mobile App uses a variety of technical methods for tracking purposes, including Web beacons. Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of websites. We also use these technical methods to analyze the traffic patterns on the Website, such as the frequency with which our users visit various parts of the Website. These technical methods may involve the transmission of information either directly to us or to another party authorized by us to collect information on our behalf. We also use these technical methods in HTML emails that we send to determine whether the recipients have opened those emails and/or clicked on links in those emails. The information from use of these technical methods may be collected in a form that is personally identifiable.

IP Addresses and Click-Stream Data

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data to analyze trends in the aggregate and administer the site.

An IP address is a number associated with the service through which you access the Internet, like your ISP (Internet service provider), your company, or your university. Standing alone, your IP address is not personally identifiable. At times, we also use IP addresses for purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers and sponsors, for example regarding the frequency with which our guests visit various parts of the Website. We may combine this information with personally identifiable information we obtain from you directly on the Website or any other of our other websites, or from third parties.

Click-stream data is information collected by our computers when you request pages from the Website. Click-stream data may include such information as the page served, the time, the source of the request, the type of browser making the request, the preceding page view and other such non-personal information. When analyzed, this data helps us analyze how visitors arrive at the Website, what type of content is most popular, what type of visitors in the aggregate are interested in particular kinds of content and advertising, and the like.

Behavioral Targeting/ Re-Targeting

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or Mobile App or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [Here](http://preferences.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

Transaction Information

If you conduct a financial or other transaction with the Website or Mobile App or subscribe for any of the products/services offered on the Website or Mobile App, we will ask you to complete an order form that will request certain information from you, including contact information, demographic information and/or financial information. In some instances, we may direct you to a third party vendor site to collect this information from you directly. Even though the collection form may have the look and feel of [www.buffalobills.com](http://www.buffalobills.com/) please be aware you will be giving your information directly to the third party vendor, and that in some instances such third party vendor's privacy policy will govern the collection of your personal information. Please reference the privacy policies available from these pages for any privacy related concerns.

We and/or our vendor will use this information to complete the financial or other transaction that you have requested, i.e. to deliver the information, products or other services that you request or purchase, to invoice you, and in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy. For your protection, financial information is collected and stored through encrypted means.

Mobile Devices

When you download and use our services, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use, operating system version, and the device identifier (or “UDID”). Certain features within the app, such as playing a game, may require you to log into your Facebook account to use them. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

We may send you push notifications from time to time in order to update you about any events or promotions that we may be running. If you no longer wish to receive these types of communications, you may turn them off at the device level.

Certain features within the app may require you to log into your Facebook account to use them. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

Geo-Location Data

We collect your location based information for the purpose of sending you location based alerts. We will only share this information with our mapping provider for the sole purpose of providing you this service. We may share your geolocation data with third parties for the purpose of them serving you ads for places (such as restaurants) in your area. If you do not wish to allow us to share your information in this manner please opt-out by contacting us at [BillsPrivacy@bills.nfl.net](mailto:BillsPrivacy@bills.nfl.net). You may opt-out of location based services at any time by editing the setting at the device level or by emailing us at [BillsPrivacy@bills.nfl.net](mailto:BillsPrivacy@bills.nfl.net).

Mobile Analytics

We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Mobile Software on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the Mobile App, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personally identifiable information you submit within the Mobile App.

3\. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED

We own the information collected on or through the Website or Mobile App. As applicable, the information you provide to us may be used to:

· contact you about the Website;

· provide you with services or information you have requested or products or services you have ordered, such as subscription plans or other products and services

· contact you relating to your membership status;

· confirm or fulfill an order you have made;

· inform you of a prize you may have won;

· promote the winning of prizes;

· monitor or improve the use of the Website or Mobile App;

· customize the advertising and content you see;

· monitor compliance with our terms and conditions of use of the Website and Mobile App; and

· provide promotional material or special offers on our behalf or on behalf of our marketing partners and/or their respective affiliates and subsidiaries and other third parties.

4\. WITH WHOM THE INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED

We will share your personally identifiable information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personally identifiable information to third parties. At times, as described below, we may share your personal information with others for various purposes:

· Agents: We employ other businesses, certain services and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, providing subscription products/services, sending email, removing repetitive information from customer lists, Website and Mobile App analysis, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These entities have access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use or disclose it for other purposes, like sending you marketing offers about their products.

· Aggregate Information: We may share aggregate information, such as demographics and Website and Mobile App usage statistics, with advertisers, sponsors or other organizations. When this type of information is shared, the other parties do not have access to your personally identifiable information.

· Option to Receive Third Party Offers: Throughout the Website and Mobile App you may be presented with an opportunity to receive information and/or marketing offers sent from third party(s). Such opportunities will give you the choice to share your personally identifiable information with such third party(s) as necessary to receive such information or marketing offers. If you do not elect to have your personally identifiable information shared, your personally identifiable information will not be shared with such third party(s). If you do choose to have your personally identifiable information shared, your personally identifiable information will be transferred to such third party(s) solely for the purpose of permitting such third party(s) to provide you with such information and marketing offers. Such third party(s) is/are not authorized by us to disclose your personally identifiable information to any other third parties. Please be advised that if you elect to provide your personally identifiable information in response to such third party(s) marketing offers or otherwise, all information you disclose to such third party(s) will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of such third party(s). We are not responsible for the privacy practices and policies of such third party(s) and, therefore, you should review the privacy practices and policies of such third party(s) prior to providing your personally identifiable information to such third party(s).

· Products or Services Offered in Partnership with Third-Party(s): Certain products and/or services available on the Website or Mobile App are provided to you in partnership with third party(s) and may require you to disclose personally identifiable information in order to register for and access such products and/or services. Such products and/or services shall identify the third party partners at the point of registration. If you elect to register for such products and/or services your personally identifiable information will be transferred to such third party(s) and will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of such third party(s). We are not responsible for the privacy practices and policies of such third party(s) and, therefore, you should review the privacy practices and policies of such third party(s) prior to providing your personally identifiable information in connection with such products and/or services.

· Subsidiaries and Affiliates: We may share your information (including, without limitation, personally identifiable information) with our subsidiaries and affiliates. If you don’t want us to share your information with our subsidiaries and affiliates, please email us at [BillsPrivacy@bills.nfl.net](mailto:BillsPrivacy@bills.nfl.net) with your request. If you visit a website that is linked to the Website, you should consult that website's privacy policy before providing any personal information.

· Legal Process: In the event we are required to respond to subpoenas, court orders, government authorities, or other legal process and when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, your personally identifiable information may be disclosed pursuant to such subpoena, court order legal process, or government authority which may be without notice to you

· Business Transfers: In the event that all or substantially all of our assets are sold or transferred to another party, or another transaction occurs in which your personally identifiable is one of business assets transferred, all personally identifiable information that has been collected and saved may be one of the business assets we transfer. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personally identifiable information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personally identifiable information.

· Non-U.S. Residents: Please note that the services are directed towards users who reside in the United States. By using the services, you consent to the collection, storage, processing, and transfer of your information in and to the United States, or other countries and territories, pursuant to the laws of the United States. While some of these countries may not offer the same level of privacy protection as your own, we commit to uphold the privacy protections as explained in this Policy.

You should be aware that when you are on the Website or Mobile App you could be directed to other websites beyond our control. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement, the "click" may take you off the Website onto a different website. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and marketing partners that may use the Website's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other websites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data or solicit personal information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. If you visit a website that is linked to the Website, you should consult that website's privacy policy before providing any personal information.

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

The Website and Mobile App incorporates reasonable safeguards to protect the security, integrity, completeness, accuracy and privacy of the personal information that we may collect and we have put into place reasonable precautions to protect such information from loss, misuse and alteration. Your personally identifiable information is transferred to our computers utilizing encryption software. Only those employees who need access to your information in order to do their jobs are allowed access. Our security policies are reviewed periodically and revised as required.

When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number and/or geo-location data) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [BillsPrivacy@bills.nfl.net](mailto:BillsPrivacy@bills.nfl.net).

7\. DATA RETENTION

We will retain your information (including geo-location data) for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [BillsPrivacy@bills.nfl.net](mailto:BillsPrivacy@bills.nfl.net). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

8\. CHAT ROOMS, FORUMS, AND MESSAGE BOARDS

The Website and Mobile App may make chat rooms, forums, commenting and message boards available to you and other users. You are not required to provide any personal information when using these areas but you may choose to do so. If you post personal information online, it will be publicly available and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. We cannot ensure the security of any information you choose to make public in a chat room, forum, or message board. Also, we cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy. Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these areas. _To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at _[BillsPrivacy@bills.nfl.net](mailto:BillsPrivacy@bills.nfl.net). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

9\. A SPECIAL NOTE FOR PARENTS CONCERNING PRIVACY

The Website is a general audience website. We do not currently knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen. If, in the future, we collect personally identifiable information from children on the Website, we will do so in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (15 U.S.C. 6501 et seq.) including, without limitation, obtaining necessary parental consent.

The Internet offers children wonderful educational and entertainment resources. Your guidance and involvement are essential to help ensure that children have a safe and rewarding online experience. We encourage you to visit the Direct Marketing Association's website at [http://www.the-dma.org](http://www.the-dma.org/) and explore the Get CyberSavvy! Program as well as the GetNetWise website [www.getnetwise.org](http://www.getnetwise.org/) to learn more about parental control tools.

10\. YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE PRIVACY POLICY AND NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY

By using the Website or Mobile App, you signify your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make a material change to the way in which we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will post a notice on the Website or Mobile App and/or send an email to users who have provided an email address prior to the change becoming effective. We will assume that you have given your permission for your information to be used under the terms of the Privacy Policy, as modified, if you do not respond to our email within thirty days or continue to use the Website thirty days after a notice is posted. Please note that you should always update your personal information to provide us with a current email address.

11\. ACCESSING/CORRECTING/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION

Upon request we will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information.

If your personally identifiable information changes (such as your email address or zip code), or if you no longer desire to have access to the Website, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update, delete or remove the personal data you have provided to us. You may request that we do so by emailing us at [BillsPrivacy@bills.nfl.net](mailto:BillsPrivacy@bills.nfl.net), signing into your online account and making the desired changes, or via mail at: Buffalo Bills, LLC, One Bills Drive, Orchard Park, NY 14127. We will respond to your request to access within thirty (30) days.

12\. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and have questions about our compliance with this law, please send an email to [BillsPrivacy@bills.nfl.net](mailto:BillsPrivacy@bills.nfl.net) or write us at CA Privacy Rights, Buffalo Bills, LLC, One Bills Drive, Orchard Park, NY 14127.

13\. THIRD-PARTY AD SERVING AND AUDIENCE AND TRAFFIC MEASUREMENT SERVICES

We may use third-parties to serve advertisements on the Services. These third parties may set their own cookies or similar web technologies to collect information about users' online activities over time and across different websites. To manage your preferences you may opt out here http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/. The Services may feature Nielsen proprietary measurement software, which will allow users to contribute to market research, such as Nielsen TV Ratings. Nielsen believes that you should have a choice about whether to contribute to our research and insights. To opt out of Nielsen measurement, you need only to activate the "Limit Ad Tracking" (for iOS devices) or "Opt out of Ads Personalization" (for Android devices) option in your devices settings. For web, please visit: http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy to learn more about the Nielsen digital measurement products and your choices in regard to them.

14\. QUESTIONS ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the privacy practices of this Website, please contact us by email at [BillsPrivacy@bills.nfl.net](mailto:BillsPrivacy@bills.nfl.net) or:

Buffalo Bills, LLC.  
One Bills Drive  
Orchard Park, NY 14127  
Attn: Website Privacy Policy
